William Edgar Borah Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General Office File, 1907-1940 (Box 1-528)
  - 1927-1928 (Box 240)
    - Letters
      - Introduction, (2 folders)
      - Recommendation
    - Levinson, Salmon O., (2 folders) (Box 254)
    - Lists
    - Mexican and Japanese colonization, Imperial Valley, Mexico
    - Mexico
    - Mexico investigation, Senate
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders); (9 folders) (Box 255)
    - Mississippi flood control (Box 256)
    - Muscle Shoals, Ala.
    - Narcotics legislation
    - National banks
    - Naturalization
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md.
    - Naval matters
    - Navy, extension of
    - Newspapers, (3 folders)
    - Nicaragua, (2 folders) (Box 257)
    - O'Brien, William J.
    - Outlawry of war, (3 folders)
    - Panama (Box 258)
    - Passports
    - Patents
    - Patronage, appointments
      - Borah, Wayne G.
      - Budge, Alfred
      - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Pension legislation
    - Personal
      - Campaign expenses
      - Public record
      - Secretary of state (Box 259)
      - Miscellaneous
    - Philippine legislation
    - Poisonous gas, outlawing of
    - Political
      - Campaign, (4 folders)
      - Idaho, miscellaneous
      - Personal, (2 folders) (Box 260)
      - Miscellaneous
    - Post Office Department
    - Post Office legislation, (2 folders)
    - Prohibition
    - Prohibition districts (Box 261)
    - Radio
    - Radio legislation
    - Railroad legislation
    - Requests for
      - Articles
      - Hearings, general reports
      - Photographs
      - Speeches, (2 folders)
    - Robins, Raymond
    - Rockwell, Irvin E.
    - Russia
    - Salaries, increase of
    - Schreiner, George A.
    - Smith-Vare cases
    - Soldier's Home, Washington, D.C.
    - Tacna and Arica affair
    - Treasury Department
    - Underwood Tariff (Box 262)
    - Veterans Bureau
    - Veterans Hospital
    - West Point, N.Y., United States Military Academy, (2 folders)
  - 1928-1929
    - Aeronautics
    - Agriculture legislation, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 263)
    - Agriculture Department
    - Alien property
      - Custodian
      - Legislation
    - Appointments
    - Appropriations
    - Applications (Box 264)
      - Pardons
      - Positions
        - A-I, (4 folders)
        - J-Y, (7 folders) (Box 265)
        - U-Z (Box 266)
        - Census
        - Idaho boys
    - Army matters
    - Articles, granted
    - Babb, James E.
    - Babson, Roger W.
    - Bank legislation
    - Bonds
    - Bonus
    - Borah, William Edgar, Special
    - Boulder Dam
    - Business notes of Mrs. E. W. Yeomans
    - Business (Box 267)
      - Income tax
      - Lodge dues
      - Taxes
      - Miscellaneous
    - Cavanah, Charles C.
    - Charity
    - China
    - Citizenship
    - Civil Service
    - Claims, (2 folders)
    - Committee
    - Committee matters, (2 folders) (Box 268)
    - Condolences
    - Congratulations
    - Congressional Library lists
    - Congressional Record
    - Cuba
    - Cuban affairs
    - Cuban investigation
    - Cumberland Falls Project, Cumberland Falls, Ky., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 269)
    - Customs
    - Debenture afterworth
    - Disarmament
    - Discharges
      - Army
      - Marine Corps
    - Documents
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Durant Prize
    - Education legislation (Box 270)
    - Fascist investigation, (3 folders)
    - Federal buildings
    - Federal Farm Board
    - Federal farm loan
    - Federal Loan Board
    - Fish
    - Food ships
    - Football tickets
    - Foreign
      - Affairs
      - Letters, (1 folder) (Box 271)
    - Freight rates
    - General information, (2 folders)
    - Haiti
    - Hart, John W.
    - Heflin, Thomas
    - Immigration, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 272)
    - Inaugural tickets
    - Inauguration
    - Income tax
    - Indian
      - Affairs
      - Legislation
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Invitations
      - California-Idaho, (8 folders)
      - Illinois-New York, (17 folders) (Box 273)
      - New York City-Wisconsin, (19 folders) (Box 274)
    - Judiciary Committee (Box 275)
    - Lasley, Sue
    - League of Nations
    - Legislation
      - American Warehousemen's Association
      - Income tax law
      - Miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Letters
      - Introduction, (2 folders)
      - Introduction, Russia (Box 276)
      - Recommendation
    - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Lists
    - Lobby investigation
    - McKaig, Ray
    - Mexico
    - Miscellaneous, (1 folder)
    - Miscellaneous, (6 folders) (Box 277)
    - Muscle Shoals, Ala.
    - National banks (Box 278)
    - Naturalization
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md.
    - Naval bill
    - Navy matters
    - Newspapers, (4 folders)
    - Nicaragua
    - Nine Power Treaty
    - Outlawry of war (Box 279)
    - Passports
    - Patents and invention
    - Patronage, appointments
      - Alaska
      - Allen, Wester J.
      - Bootle, W. A.
      - Budge, Alfred
      - Cotton, Joseph P.
      - Court of claims
      - Dubois, Fred T.
      - Farm Board
      - Glassie, Henry H. (Box 280)
      - Hart, John W.
      - Hopkins, Richard J., (3 folders)
      - Hughes, Wilburn P.
      - Marsters, Elias
      - Martin, G. H.
      - Memphis, Tenn., Post Office
      - Public Lands Committee (Box 281)
      - Secretary of state
      - Secretary of interior
      - Snook, John W.
      - Tax appeals
      - United States District Attorneyship of Idaho
      - Watson, Albert L., (2 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 282)
    - Pension legislation, (2 folders)
    - Personal, (3 folders)
    - Philippines
    - Political
      - Idaho government
      - Miscellaneous
    - Post Office Department (Box 283)
    - Post Office legislation
    - Prohibition, (3 folders)
    - Public Health Service
    - Radio
    - Radio legislation
    - Railroad legislation
    - Railroads
    - Recommendation of Edwin L. Davis
    - Requests for
      - Articles
      - Hearings, general reports (Box 284)
      - Photographs
      - Records
      - Speeches, (2 folders)
    - Robins, Raymond
    - Rockwell, Irvin E.
    - Russia
    - Salaries
    - Shearer, William B., investigation
    - Shipstead Resolution
    - Soldiers Home, Washington, D.C.
    - Stock exchange investigation
    - Tariff, (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 285)
    - Veterans Bureau
    - Veterans Hospital
    - West Point, N.Y., United States Military Academy
    - World Court
  - 1929-1930 (Box 286)
    - Aeronautics
    - Agriculture, (4 folders)
    - Alien property custodian
    - Applications
      - Pardons
      - Positions
        - Census
        - Idaho boys
        - A-Y, (6 folders) (Box 287)
    - Appointments (Box 288)
    - Appropriations
    - Army matters
    - Articles, (2 folders)
    - Babb, James E.
    - Bank legislation
    - Bonds
    - Bonus
    - Borah, William Edgar, special data brought from Boise, Idaho
    - Business
      - Income tax
      - Yeomans, W. E., note
      - Miscellaneous
    - Charity
    - China
    - Citizenship
    - Claims, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 289)
    - Committee
      - London, England, treaties
      - Matters
      - Miscellaneous
    - Congratulations (Box 290)
    - Congressional Library list
    - Congressional Record
    - Cuba
    - Cumberland Falls Project, Cumberland Falls, Ky.
    - Customs
    - Disarmament, (2 folders)
    - Discharges, army
    - Documents
      - General
      - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Educational legislation
    - Fascist investigation, Heflin Resolution
    - Federal buildings (Box 291)
    - Federal Farm Board
    - Federal Farm Loan Board
    - Fish
    - Fish Congressional Committee
    - Foreign
      - Affairs
      - Letters, (2 folders)
    - Freight rate
    - General, (2 folders)
    - Haiti (Box 292)
    - Immigration, (2 folders)
    - Income tax
    - Indian affairs
    - Internal Revenue
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Invitations
      - Alabama-Colorado, (4 folders)
      - District of Columbia-Montana, (17 folders) (Box 293)
      - Nebraska-Wyoming, (20 folders) (Box 294)
    - Lasley, Sue (Box 295)
    - Legislation
      - Bus bill
      - Equity receivership
      - Flathead power proposition
      - H.R. 9557
      - Income tax law
      - Narcotics (H.R. 11143)
      - Norris bill (S. 4357)
      - Passport fees, (2 folders)
      - Wainwright Resolution (Box 296)
      - Williamson bill (H.R. 8574)
      - World War I veterans
      - Miscellaneous, (5 folders)
    - Letters (Box 297)
      - Introduction, (2 folders)
      - Introduction, Russia
      - Recommendation
    - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Lobby Committee, James Cannon, Jr.
    - McKaig, Ray
    - Mexico
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders); (5 folders) (Box 298)
    - Muscle, Ala.
    - National banks
    - Naturalization
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md. (Box 299)
    - Navy
      - Legislation
      - Matters
    - Newspapers, (2 folders)
    - Nicaragua
    - Outlawry of war
    - Passports
    - Patents
    - Patronage
      - Appointments
        - Alaska
        - Coeur D'Alene, Idaho, land office
        - DuBois, Fred T.
        - Hughes, Charles Evans, (2 folders) (Box 300)
        - Internal Revenue collector, Idaho
        - Interstate Commerce Commission
        - MacNider, Hanford
        - O'Toole, Mary
        - Parker, John J., (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 301)
        - Roberts, Owen J.
        - Thatcher, Thomas D.
        - United States District Attorneyship, Idaho
        - United States Marshall, Idaho
        - Walters, Jacobs D.
        - Prohibition director
        - Miscellaneous
    - Pension legislation, (1 folder) (Box 302)
    - Personal, (2 folders)
    - Philippines
    - Political
      - Idaho
        - Governorship
        - Miscellaneous
      - Personal, (2 folders)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 303)
    - Post Office Department
    - Post Office legislation
    - Primary
    - Prohibition, (3 folders)
    - Prohibition, Herbert and Suinn, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 304)
    - Puerto Rico
    - Radio
    - Radio legislation
    - Railroad legislation
    - Requests for
      - Bills
      - Hearings
      - Photographs
      - Speeches
      - Treaties
    - Retirement
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Robins, Raymond
    - Rockwell, Irvin E.
    - Russia, (2 folders)
    - Salaries, increase of (Box 305)
    - Silver
    - Soldiers Home, Washington, D.C.
    - Tariff, (5 folders)
    - Tariff, lumber (Box 306)
    - Tax reduction
    - Taxing property in national parks
    - Treasury Department
    - Veterans Bureau
    - Veterans Hospital
    - Veterans legislation
    - West Point, N.Y., United States Military Academy
    - World Court, (3 folders)
  - 1930-1931 (Box 307)
    - Aeronautics
    - Agriculture, (2 folders)
    - Agriculture Data for Progressive Committee, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 308)
    - Applications
      - Pardons
      - Positions
        - Deputy Marshal
        - Idaho boys
        - A-D, (3 folders)
        - E-Y, (7 folders) (Box 309)
    - Appointments, (2 folders) (Box 310)
    - Appropriations
    - Army matters
    - Articles, (2 folders)
    - Babb, James E.
    - Bank legislation
    - Bonds
    - Bonus
    - Borah, Charles F.
    - Borah, William Edgar, special
    - Business
      - Income tax
      - Lodge dues
      - Taxes (Box 311)
      - Miscellaneous
    - Butler, Smedley
    - Charity
    - China
    - Citizenship
    - Claims, (2 folders)
    - Coals
    - Coast Guard
    - Commerce Department
    - Committee matters
    - Committee miscellaneous
    - Condolences (Box 312)
    - Congratulations
    - Congressional Library lists
    - Congressional Record
    - Cuba
    - Cumberland Falls Project, Cumberland Falls, Ky.
    - Customs
    - Davis, James J., unseating of
    - Disarmament
    - Discharges
      - Army
      - Marine Corps
      - Navy
    - Documents
    - Economic situation
    - Economy, relief question
    - Educational legislation
    - Federal buildings
    - Federal Farm Board
    - Federal farm loan (Box 313)
    - Federal Land Bank
    - Federal Reserve
    - Fish
    - Fish Investigating Committee
    - Foreign
      - Affairs
      - Letters, (3 folders)
    - Freight rates
    - General, (3 folders) (Box 314)
    - Haiti
    - Hoover, Herbert, proposal
    - Immigration, (3 folders)
    - Income tax (Box 315)
    - Indian
      - Affairs
      - Legislation
    - Internal Revenue
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Invitations
      - Alabama-Illinois, (12 folders)
      - Indiana-Ohio, (20 folders) (Box 316)
      - Oklahoma-Wyoming, (14 folders) (Box 317)
    - Justice Department
    - Lasley, Sue
    - Legislation
      - Bus bill
      - Capper-Reed bill
      - Doctors bill (S. 4582)
      - "Forty-four hour week" (H.R. 6603)
      - Heflin Bill
      - Navy
      - St. Lawrence River (Box 318)
      - S. 5309
      - Veterans compensation certificates, cashing of
      - World War veterans
      - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Letters
      - Introduction
      - Introduction, Russia, (2 folders)
      - Recommendation (Box 319)
    - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Lists
    - McKaig, Ray
    - Mexico
    - Miscellaneous, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 320)
    - Muscle Shoals, Ala.
    - National banks
    - National banks, Franklin loan, New York, N.Y.
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md., (2 folders)
    - Navy
      - Holiday
      - Matters
    - Newspapers, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 321)
    - Nicaragua
    - Oil, (3 folders)
    - Passports (Box 322)
    - Patents and inventions
    - Patronage, appointments
      - Alaska
      - Assay office, Boise, Id.
      - Board of Tax Appeals
      - Bradley, Fred A.
      - Connolly, Christopher P.
      - Groner, Lawrence D.
      - Judgeship to fill seat of Charles. C. Cavanah
      - Marsters, Elias
      - Postmastership, Boise, Idaho
      - Register of Land Office, Blackfoot, Idaho
      - United States Circuit Court of Appeals
      - United States Marshalship, Idaho (Box 323)
      - Miscellaneous
    - Pension legislation
    - Personal, (2 folders)
    - Political
      - Idaho, (2 folders)
      - Personal (Box 324)
      - Miscellaneous
    - Post Office Department
    - Post Office legislation
    - Primary
    - Prohibition
    - Public Health Service
    - Public ownership
    - Radio
    - Radio legislation
    - Railroad legislation
    - Requests for
      - Bills
      - Hearings
      - Photographs (Box 325)
      - Speeches
      - Speeches, Russia
      - Treaties
    - Retirement
    - Robins, Raymond
    - Rockwell, Irvin E.
    - Russia, (2 folders) (Box 326)
    - Russia, positions, (3 folders)
    - Silver, (1 folder)
    - Silver, (2 folders) (Box 327)
    - Soldiers Home, Washington, D.C.
    - Tariff
    - Tariff, oil and wheat
    - Taxes
    - Treasury Department
    - Unemployment situation
    - Veterans Bureau
    - Veterans Bureau, Hospitals
    - Washburn, Robert M. (Box 328)
    - West Point, N.Y., United States Military Academy
    - World Court
  - 1931-1932
    - Aeronautics
    - Agriculture, (2 folders)
    - Airmail route
    - Applications
      - Pardons
      - Positions
        - Idaho boys
        - A-M, (7 folders) (Box 329)
        - N-W, (3 folders) (Box 330)
    - Appointments with Borah, (2 folders)
    - Appropriations
    - Army matters
    - Articles, (2 folders) (Box 331)
    - Bank legislation, (2 folders)
    - Beer legislation
    - Bonds
    - Bonus
    - Borah, William E., personal
    - Business
      - Automobile, LaSalle
      - Income tax
      - Lodge dues
      - Storage receipts
      - Taxes (Box 332)
      - Yeomans, William E., note
      - Miscellaneous
    - Charity
    - China
    - Citizenship
    - Claims, (4 folders)
    - Coast Guard (Box 333)
    - Committee
      - St. Lawrence River Treaty
      - Miscellaneous
    - Committee matters, (2 folders)
    - Condolences (Box 334)
    - Congratulations
    - Congressional Library lists
    - Congressional Record
    - Crump-Red Cross controversy
    - Cuba
    - Currency
    - Debt cancellation speech
    - Debt settlement
    - Depletion of mines
    - Disarmament (Box 335)
    - Discharges
      - Army
      - Navy
    - Documents
      - General
      - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Economic situation
    - Educational legislation
    - Farm legislation
    - Farm loans
    - Federal buildings
    - Federal Farm Board
    - Federal Farm Loan, (1 folder) (Box 336)
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board
    - Federal Land Bank
    - Federal Power Commission
    - Federal Reserve Board
    - Fish
    - Fish Investigating Committee
    - Foreign
      - Affairs, (2 folders)
      - Letters, (2 folders) (Box 337)
      - Relations
    - General, (3 folders)
    - Gumberg, Alex
    - Hart, John W. (Box 338)
    - Hawaii
    - Heflin-Bankhead seat
    - Home Loan Bank bill
    - Hungary
    - Immigration, (4 folders)
    - Income tax
    - Indian affairs
    - Indian legislation
    - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 339)
    - Invitations
      - Arkansas-Maine, (17 folders)
      - Maryland-New York City, (16 folders) (Box 340)
      - South Dakota-Wisconsin, (8 folders) (Box 341)
    - Labor Department
    - Lasley, Sue
    - Lausanne, Switzerland, speech
    - Legislation
      - Birth control
      - Bonus, soldiers in Washington, D.C.
      - Federal Power Commission Act
      - Home Loan Bank bill
      - National Economy Act, Section 207-907
      - Oddie Bill
      - Soldiers bonus, (2 folders) (Box 342)
      - Veterans hospitalization
      - Vocational education
      - Miscellaneous, (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box 343)
    - Letters of introduction, (2 folders)
    - Letters of recommendation
    - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Lists
    - McKaig, Ray
    - Mail contracts
    - Mexico
    - Miscellaneous, (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 344)
    - National banks
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md., (2 folders) (Box 345)
    - Navy matters
    - Oil
    - Outlawry of war
    - Newspapers, (6 folders)
    - Nicaragua (Box 346)
    - Passports
    - Patents, inventions
    - Patronage, appointments
      - Receivership
      - Miscellaneous, (4 folders)
    - Pension legislation (Box 347)
    - Personal
      - Public record
      - Miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Philippine independence
    - Political
      - Idaho, (2 folders)
      - Personal (Box 348)
      - Miscellaneous
    - Post Office Department
    - Post Office legislation
    - Prohibition, (2 folders)
    - Public Health Service
    - Radio
    - Radio legislation
    - Railroad legislation
    - Reconstruction Finance Corp.
    - Requests for (Box 349)
      - Bills
      - Hearings
      - Photographs
      - Speeches
      - Treaties
    - Retirement
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Robins, Raymond
    - Rockwell, Irvin E.
    - Russia, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 350)
    - Russian positions
    - Salaries, reduction of, (3 folders)
    - Schreiner-McGuire
    - Silver, (2 folders)
    - Silver speech (Box 351)
    - Soldiers Home, Washington, D.C.
    - St. Lawrence River Treaty
    - Subcommittee appointments
    - Tariff
    - Taxation, (4 folders)
    - Treasury Department (Box 352)
    - Unemployment situation
    - Veterans Bureau
    - Veterans Bureau Hospital
    - Washburn, Robert M.
    - West Point, N.Y., United States Military Academy, (2 folders)
    - Wilkerson, James H.
    - World Court
  - 1932-1933
    - Aeronautics
    - Agricultural matters, (2 folders) (Box 353)
    - Agriculture
      - Allotment plan
      - Financing far mortgages
      - New farm bill
    - Applications for pardons
    - Applications for positions
      - Idaho boys
      - United States Marshall
      - A-D
      - E-Z, (5 folders) (Box 354)
      - Appointments, Borah (Box 355)
    - Appropriations
    - Army matters
    - Articles, (2 folders)
    - Assay office
    - Babb, James E.
    - Bank Legislation
    - Bank legislation, 1st National Bank of Idaho (Box 356)
    - Beer legislation
    - Bonds
    - Bonus
    - Borah, William Edgar, personal
    - Brossard-Overton investigations
    - Business
      - Automobile, LaSalle
      - Income tax
      - Lodge dues
      - Taxes
      - Miscellaneous
    - Charity
    - Citizenship
    - Civil Service
    - Civil Service Commission
    - Claims, (2 folders)
    - Committee (Box 357)
      - Arms embargo
      - Matters
      - St. Lawrence Treaty
      - Miscellaneous
    - Condolences
    - Congratulations
    - Congressional Library lists
    - Congressional Record
    - Cuba
    - Currency, (2 folders) (Box 358)
    - Customs
    - Dictatorial powers
    - Disarmament, history of
    - Discharge, navy
    - Documents
    - Economic situation
    - Educational legislation
    - Farm Credit Administration
    - Federal buildings
    - Federal Farm Board (Box 359)
    - Federal Farm loans
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board
    - Federal Land Bank
    - Federal relief
    - Federal Reserve Bank
    - Federal Trade Commission
    - Fish
    - Foreign affairs
    - Foreign affairs, German atrocities, Jews
    - Foreign debt, (1 folder) (Box 360)
    - Foreign letters
    - Freight rates
    - General information, (2 folders)
    - Gold, (2 folders)
    - Haiti
    - Hawaii
    - Home Loan Bank law, repeal of (Box 361)
    - Hungary
    - Immigration
    - Inaugural tickets
    - Income tax
    - Indian affairs
    - Indian legislation
    - Internal Revenue
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Invitations
      - Arkansas-Idaho, (8 folders)
      - Illinois-Wyoming, (31 folders) (Box 362)
    - Joint stock land banks (Box 363)
    - Justice Department
    - Lasley, Sue
    - Legislation
      - Adjusted Service Certificates
      - Birth control bill
      - Compulsory retirement bill
      - Deportation bill
      - Excess profits tax
      - Industrial recovery bill
      - Sales tax
      - Short selling
      - Taxes
      - Thirty hour work week
      - Legislation (Box 364)
      - Veterans
      - Miscellaneous, (5 folders)
    - Letters of introduction
    - Letters of introduction, Russia
    - Letters of recommendation
    - Levinson, Salmon O. (Box 365)
    - Lists
    - Long, Huey
    - McKaig, Ray
    - Mail contracts
    - Manuscripts, (2 folders)
    - Mexican Claims Commission
    - Mines and mining
    - Miscellaneous, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 366)
    - National bank
    - National Recovery Act
    - National Recovery Administration
    - Naturalization
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md., (2 folders) (Box 367)
    - Navy matters
    - "New" bank bill, (2 folders)
    - Newspapers, (2 folders) (Box 368)
    - Newspapers, William Allen White matter
    - Oil dictatorship
    - Passports
    - Patents, inventions
    - Patronage, appointments
      - Arney, C. E.
      - Assay office, Boise, Idaho
      - Bingham, Judge
      - Director, Reconstruction Finance Corp.
      - Idaho
      - Newton, Walter H.
      - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 369)
    - Pension and compensation cuts
    - Pension legislation
    - Personal, (2 folders)
    - Philippine legislation
    - Political
      - Idaho
      - Miscellaneous
    - Post Office Department
    - Post Office legislation
    - Prohibition, (2 folders) (Box 370)
    - Radio
    - Railroad legislation
    - Reciprocity with Canada
    - Reconstruction Finance Corp. loans, (2 folders)
    - Reforestation
    - Requests for
      - Bills
      - Hearings
      - Photographs, autographs (Box 371)
      - Speeches
      - Speeches, Russia
      - Treaties
    - Robins, Raymond
    - Rockwell, Irvin E.
    - Russia
      - Editorials on recognition
      - General, (4 folders)
      - Positions (Box 372)
      - Trial of British subject
    - Salaries, reduction of
    - Schreiner, George A.
    - Silver, (2 folders)
    - Soldiers Home, Washington, D.C.